A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exhibitions and Events, 1963-1999; 3
  - Exhibition, Publicity and Events Miscellaneous, 3
    - Korea 18th Century - Printer (Box 323, Folder 3735)
    - Korea 18th Century - Publicity (Box 323, Folder 3736)
    - Korea 18th Century - Preliminary and Post Production (Box 323, Folder 3737)
    - Korea 18th Century - Translators Correspondence (Box 323, Folder 3738)
    - Korea 18th Century - Grants (Box 323, Folder 3739)
    - Korea 18th Century - Schedules and Budgets, 1990-1993 (Box 323, Folder 3740)
    - Korea 18th Century - Philip Morris Correspondence, 1993 (Box 323, Folder 3741)
    - Korea 18th Century - Special Sales and Shipping, In-House, 1993 (Box 323, Folder 3742)
    - Korea 18th Century - Editor, 1993 (Box 324, Folder 3743)
    - Korea 18th Century - Contracts, 1993 (Box 324, Folder 3744)
    - Korea 18th Century - Designer, 1993 (Box 324, Folder 3745)
    - Korea 18th Century - Photographer, 1992-1993 (Box 324, Folder 3746)
    - Buddha of the Future - Preliminary and Post-Production (Box 324, Folder 3747)
    - Buddha of the Future - Author Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 324, Folder 3748)
    - Buddha of the Future - Schedules and Budgets, 1993-1994 (Box 324, Folder 3749)
    - Buddha of the Future - Contracts (Box 324, Folder 3750)
    - Buddha of the Future - Editor/Style, 1993-1994 (Box 324, Folder 3751)
    - Buddha of the Future - Designer, 1993-1994 (Box 324, Folder 3752)
    - Asia-America Artist's Catalogue Copies (Box 324, Folder 3753)
    - Asia/America Artist's Catalogue Shipping and Comps (Box 324, Folder 3754)
    - Out of Asia - Designer, 1993-1995 (Box 325, Folder 3755)
    - Out of Asia - Photographer, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3756)
    - Out of Asia - Printer, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3758)
    - Out of Asia - Front Matter, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3759)
    - Out of Asia - Author Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 325, Folder 3760)
    - Out of Asia - Schedules and Budgets, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3761)
    - Out of Asia - Contracts, 1994 (Box 325, Folder 3762)
    - Out of Asia - Co-publisher, 1992-1993 (Box 325, Folder 3763)
    - Out of Asia - Editor, 1993 (Box 325, Folder 3764)
    - Out of Asia - Preliminary and Post-Production, 1992-1994 (Box 325, Folder 3765)
    - Out of Asia, 1991-1994 (Box 325, Folder 3766)
    - Japanese Screens - Correspondence Idemitsu, 1993-1996 (Box 325, Folder 3767)
    - Cultures at Crossroads (Box 326, Folder 3768)
    - Cultures at Crossroads - Co-Publisher (Box 326, Folder 3769)
    - Cultures at Crossroads - Correspondence with ANG, 1992 (Box 326, Folder 3770)
    - Cultures at Crossroads - Correspondence with Cande Nest, 1992 (Box 326, Folder 3771)
    - Cultures at Crossroads - Design, 1992 (Box 326, Folder 3772)
    - Cultures at Crossroads - ANG Programs Publications, 1992 (Box 326, Folder 3773)
    - Iranian Ceramics, 1963 (Box 326, Folder 3774)
    - The Art of the Korean Potter, 1968 (Box 326, Folder 3775)
    - Japanese Art of the Heian Period, 1967 (Box 326, Folder 3776)
    - The Arts of Tibet, 1969 (Box 326, Folder 3777)
    - Ritual Vessels of the Bronze Age, China, 1968 (Box 326, Folder 3778)
    - Chinese Ceramics Progressive Proofs (Box 326, Folder 3779)
    - Masterpieces of Asian Art in American Collections II, 1970 (Box 326, Folder 3780)
    - Japanese Screens - Translators (Box 326, Folder 3781)
    - Japanese Screens - Editor, 1995 (Box 326, Folder 3782)
    - Japanese Screens - Designer, 1994-1995 (Box 326, Folder 3783)
    - Japanese Screens - Slides, 1996 (Box 326, Folder 3784)
    - Japanese Screens - Front Matter, 1995 (Box 326, Folder 3785)
    - Japanese Screens - Takeuchi Essay, 1995 (Box 326, Folder 3786)
    - Japanese Screens - Yamene Essay (Box 327, Folder 3787)
    - Japanese Screens - Kuroda Essay, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3788)
    - Japanese Screens - Entries on Objects, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3789)
    - Japanese Screens - Captions, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3790)
    - Japanese Screens - Selected Bibliography, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3791)
    - Japanese Screens - Back Matter (Box 327, Folder 3792)
    - Japanese Screens - Photos, Transparencies, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3793)
    - Japanese Screens - Idemitsu Visuals, 1995 (Box 327, Folder 3794)
    - Collection Catalogue - Preliminary and Post-Production, 1992-1995 (Box 328, Folder 3795)
    - Collection Catalogue - General, 1991-1995 (Box 328, Folder 3796)
    - Collection Catalogue - Chase, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3797)
    - Collection Catalogue - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3798)
    - Collection Catalogue - Schedules and Budgets, 1993-1994 (Box 328, Folder 3799)
    - Collection Catalogue - Grants, 1993-1994 (Box 328, Folder 3800)
    - Collection Catalogue - Contracts, 1994-1995 (Box 328, Folder 3801)
    - Collection Catalogue - Editor, 1993-1994 (Box 328, Folder 3802)
    - Collection Catalogue - Designer, 1993-1995 (Box 328, Folder 3803)
    - Collection Catalogue - Photographers, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3804)
    - Collection Catalogue - Production, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3805)
    - Collection Catalogue - Printer - Four Colour Imports, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3806)
    - Collection Catalogue - Front Matter, 1994 (Box 328, Folder 3807)
    - Collection Catalogue - Lee Essays, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3808)
    - Collection Catalogue - Catalogue Entries, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3809)
    - Collection Catalogue, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3810)
    - Collection Catalogue - Documentation, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3811)
    - Collection Catalogue - Bibliography, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3812)
    - Collection Catalogue - Appendix, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3813)
    - Collection Catalogue - Index, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3814)
    - Collection Catalogue - Credits, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3815)
    - Collection Catalogue - Captions, 1994 (Box 329, Folder 3816)
    - Collection Catalogue - Photos, Transparencies, Slides, 1995 (Box 329, Folder 3817)
    - Collection Catalogue - Rockefeller Collection Catalogue - Photography (Box 329, Folder 3818)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Invitation, 1994 (Box 330, Folder 3819)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Graphics, 1994 (Box 330, Folder 3820)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Panels, 1994 (Box 330, Folder 3821)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Map, 1994 (Box 330, Folder 3822)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Looking at Art of Asia Society - Teacher's Guide, 1994 (Box 330, Folder 3823)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Labels (Box 331, Folder 3824)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Lecture (Box 331, Folder 3825)
    - JDR 3rd Collection, 1994 (Box 331, Folder 3826)
    - JDR 3rd Collection - Handouts, 1994 (Box 331, Folder 3827)
    - Korean Art - Slide Set (Box 331, Folder 3828)
    - Korean Art - Teachers Guide (Box 331, Folder 3829)
    - Korean Art - General, 1992-1994 (Box 331, Folder 3830)
    - Korean Art - Catalogue, 1993 (Box 331, Folder 3831)
    - Korean Art - Lobby Signage, 1993-1994 (Box 331, Folder 3832)
    - Korean Art - Graphics, 1993-1994 (Box 332, Folder 3833)
    - Korean Art - Graphics LACMA, 1994 (Box 332, Folder 3834)
    - Korean Art - Brochure, 1993 (Box 332, Folder 3835)
    - Korean Art - LACMA Brochure, 1994 (Box 332, Folder 3836)
    - Japanese Screens - Schedules and Budgets, 1992-1995 (Box 332, Folder 3837)
    - Japanese Screens - Contracts, 1995 (Box 333, Folder 3838)
    - Japanese Screens - General, 1994-1995 (Box 333, Folder 3839)
    - Japanese Screens - Preliminary and Post-Publication, 1995 (Box 333, Folder 3840)
    - Japanese Screens - Correspondence Takeuchi, 1994-1995 (Box 333, Folder 3841)
    - Visions of Asia - Objects (Box 333, Folder 3842)
    - Undercurrents in the Floating World - Reprint, 1993 (Box 333, Folder 3843)
    - Past Publications, 1993-1994 (Box 333, Folder 3844)
    - Tucci, Tibet, 1994 (Box 333, Folder 3845)
    - PEW Charitable Trust, 1995 (Box 333, Folder 3846)
    - NEK Chand Sculpture, 1996 (Box 333, Folder 3847)
    - Japanese Screens - Teachers Giode, 1995 (Box 333, Folder 3848)
    - Japanese Screens - Handout (Box 334, Folder 3849)
    - Japanese Screens - Photo Blowups (Box 334, Folder 3850)
    - Japanese Screens - Graphics, 1995-1996 (Box 334, Folder 3851)
    - Japanese Screens, 1995 (Box 334, Folder 3852)
    - Japanese Screens - Labels, 1995 (Box 334, Folder 3853)
    - Japanese Screens - Panels (Box 334, Folder 3854)
    - Japanese Screens - Comment Book (Box 334, Folder 3855)
    - Japanese Screens - Catalogue - Shipping, Distribution (Box 334, Folder 3856)
    - Ceramics - Panels, 1995 (Box 334, Folder 3857)
    - Ceramics - Meiyintang Ceramics (Box 334, Folder 3858)
    - Ceramics - Graphics (Box 335, Folder 3859)
    - Ceramics - Meiyintang Ceramics - Invitation, 1994-1995 (Box 335, Folder 3860)
    - Ceramics - Meiyintang Ceramics - Brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 335, Folder 3861)
    - Ceramics - Labels (Box 335, Folder 3862)
    - Ceramics - Maps (Box 335, Folder 3863)
    - Ceramics - Final Graphics (Box 336, Folder 3864)
    - Cultures at Crossroads (CAC) - Visuals, Orientation (Box 336, Folder 3865)
    - Cultures at Crossroads (CAC) - Photos (Box 336, Folder 3866)
    - Cultures at Crossroads (CAC) - Orientation Photos (Box 336, Folder 3867)
    - Japanese Screens - Invitations, 1995 (Box 336, Folder 3868)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Final Copy Graphics, 1993 (Box 337, Folder 3869)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Graphics, 1992-1993 (Box 337, Folder 3870)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Nelson Atkins, 1993 (Box 337, Folder 3871)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Panels (Box 337, Folder 3872)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Data for Entry Notes (Box 337, Folder 3873)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Labels (Box 337, Folder 3874)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Labels (Box 338, Folder 3875)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Correspondence with Braziller, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 3876)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Design, 1992 (Box 338, Folder 3877)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Catalogue Map (Box 338, Folder 3878)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Correspondence - GGL Editors (Box 338, Folder 3879)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Editorial (Box 338, Folder 3880)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Fact Sheet (Box 338, Folder 3881)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Exhibiton Map (Box 338, Folder 3882)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Contract with Braziller (Box 338, Folder 3883)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Contract with Mapin (Box 338, Folder 3884)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Catalogue - Mapin (Box 338, Folder 3885)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Co-Publisher, 1991-1992 (Box 338, Folder 3886)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Time Line Panel (Box 338, Folder 3887)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Bills Paid (Box 338, Folder 3888)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Budgets, Financial, 1992-1993 (Box 338, Folder 3889)
    - Indian Temple Sculpture (Box 339, Folder 3890)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Correpondence with Authors, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 3891)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Design, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 3892)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Mock-Up Material, 1992 (Box 339, Folder 3893)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Sample Plans (Box 339, Folder 3894)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Arch. Terms Glossary (Box 339, Folder 3895)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Graham Foundation (Box 339, Folder 3896)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Adminstration, 1988-1991 (Box 339, Folder 3897)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Press Releases, 1993 (Box 339, Folder 3898)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Opening (Box 339, Folder 3899)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Booking Letters, General Tour, 1991-1992 (Box 339, Folder 3900)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Watercolor Exhibition Burke Room (Box 339, Folder 3901)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Michael Meister (Box 339, Folder 3902)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - American Airlines, 1993 (Box 339, Folder 3903)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Comp. Catalogues (Box 339, Folder 3904)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Development (Box 339, Folder 3905)
    - Devine Couples - Education (Box 339, Folder 3906)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Budget (Box 339, Folder 3907)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Film Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 339, Folder 3908)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Fact Sheet, 1992-1993 (Box 339, Folder 3909)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Press Articles, 1993 (Box 340, Folder 3910)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Phyllis Granoff, 1991-1992 (Box 340, Folder 3911)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Michael Willis, 1991-1992 (Box 340, Folder 3912)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - India Tourism, 1992 (Box 340, Folder 3913)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Air India, 1993 (Box 340, Folder 3914)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - IBM, 1991 (Box 340, Folder 3915)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Hyatt Hotels Corporation, 1992 (Box 340, Folder 3916)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Coca Cola Foundation, 1992 (Box 340, Folder 3917)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Fundraising, 1992-1993 (Box 340, Folder 3918)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Indo-US Subcommission, Travel in India, 1990-1992 (Box 340, Folder 3919)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - India Trip 1990 (Box 340, Folder 3920)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Indo-US Subcommission Research Trip, 1988 (Box 340, Folder 3921)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Vishakha Correspondence/Travel, 1989-1991 (Box 340, Folder 3922)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Getty Grant, 1992 (Box 340, Folder 3923)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Europe Trip, 1989 (Box 341, Folder 3924)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Installation (Box 341, Folder 3925)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Design (Box 341, Folder 3926)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Insurance (Box 341, Folder 3927)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Description (Box 341, Folder 3928)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Prof. Chattaopadhyaya, 1990-1991 (Box 341, Folder 3929)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Jawaharlal Nehru University, 1988-1992 (Box 341, Folder 3930)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Asian Art Museum of San Franscisco, 1990 (Box 341, Folder 3931)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - High Museum of Art, 1991 (Box 341, Folder 3932)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Kimbell Art Museum, 1991 (Box 341, Folder 3933)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Museum of Fine Arts, 1991-1992 (Box 341, Folder 3934)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1991 (Box 341, Folder 3935)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Brooklyn Museum (Box 341, Folder 3936)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Mrs. Alsdorf, 1992 (Box 341, Folder 3937)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Art Institute of Chicago, 1987-1990 (Box 341, Folder 3938)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Mr. Stuart Brown, 1991 (Box 341, Folder 3939)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Ford Collection (Box 341, Folder 3940)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Lenders/Venues (Box 341, Folder 3941-3962A)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Ashmolean Museum (Box 341, Folder 3963)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Royal Ontario Museum (Box 341, Folder 3964)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Mr. Irving (Box 341, Folder 3965)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - National Gallery of Canada (Box 341, Folder 3966)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - NEH (Box 341, Folder 3967)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Grant Text (Box 341, Folder 3968)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - National Film Development Corporation of India (Box 341, Folder 3969)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Barbara Stoler Miller (Box 341, Folder 3970)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Donald Stadtner (Box 341, Folder 3971)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Object List of Venues (Box 342, Folder 3972)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Press (Box 342, Folder 3973)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Government Museum (Box 342, Folder 3974)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Guest Lists, 1993 (Box 342, Folder 3975)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - National Museum, New Delhi, 1992-1993 (Box 342, Folder 3976)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - General Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 342, Folder 3977)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Jiwaji University, 1988-1990 (Box 342, Folder 3978)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Gwalior Museum, 1990 (Box 342, Folder 3979)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Photography (Box 342, Folder 3980)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Programs, 1991-1993 (Box 342, Folder 3981)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Publications, Mailing List, 1991 (Box 342, Folder 3982)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Publicity, 1992-1993 (Box 343, Folder 3983)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers - Exhibit - Registrar, 1990 (Box 343, Folder 3984)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit (GGL) - Slides (Box 343, Folder 3985)
    - Trade Routes - Comments (Box 343, Folder 3986)
    - Guywell Photo Show (Box 343, Folder 3987)
    - Mandala - Panels and Charts (Box 343, Folder 3988)
    - Mandala - Graphics, 1997-1999 (Box 343, Folder 3989)
    - Mandala (Box 343, Folder 3990)
    - Mandala - Exhibition Space (Box 343, Folder 3991)
    - Mandala - Thames and Hudson, 1997 (Box 343, Folder 3992)
    - Mandala - Photography, 1997 (Box 343, Folder 3993)
    - Hong Kong - Photography, 1997 (Box 344, Folder 3994-3996)
    - Hong Kong - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 344, Folder 3997)
    - Hong Kong - Bulletin Board Articles (Box 344, Folder 3998-3999)
    - Hong Kong - Graphics, 1997 (Box 345, Folder 4000)
    - Hong Kong - Panels (Box 345, Folder 4001)
    - Hong Kong - Labels (Box 345, Folder 4002)
    - Kotah - Graphics, 1997 (Box 345, Folder 4003)
    - Kotah - Panels, 1997 (Box 345, Folder 4004)
    - Kotah (Box 345, Folder 4005)
    - Kotah - Invitations (Box 346, Folder 4006)
    - Kotah - Labels (Box 346, Folder 4007)
    - ICA - Catalogue Permissions Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 346, Folder 4008)
    - ICA - Visuals Returned (Box 346, Folder 4009)
    - ICA - Slides on Loan (Box 346, Folder 4010)
    - Divine Couples, Lenders, Venues, Cincinnati Art Museum (Box 346, Folder 4011)
    - India Symposium, 1993 June 12 (Box 346, Folder 4012)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Catalogue (Box 346, Folder 4013)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Bills Paid, 1993 (Box 347, Folder 4014)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Darielle Mason, 1991-1992 (Box 347, Folder 4015)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Patrick George (Box 347, Folder 4016)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Catalogue Bills Paid (Box 347, Folder 4017)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - University of California, 1988 (Box 347, Folder 4018)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Tom Wong (Box 347, Folder 4019)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Staatliche Museen Preussischer, 1990 (Box 347, Folder 4020)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Peter Stern (Box 347, Folder 4021)
    - Dreamings - The Art of Aboriginal Australia (Box 347, Folder 4022)
    - Dreamings/Braziller, 1991-1996 (Box 347, Folder 4023)
    - Sing Tao Agreement, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4024)
    - Hong Kong Photography Catalogue, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4025)
    - Hong Kong - Press, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4026)
    - Hong Kong - Co-Publisher, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4027)
    - Hong Kong - Photography, 1996 (Box 347, Folder 4028)
    - Hong Kong - Permissions, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4029)
    - Hong Kong - Design, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4030)
    - Hong Kong - Distribution, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4031)
    - Hong Kong - Invoices, Expenses, 1997 (Box 347, Folder 4032)
    - Hong Kong - Contents (Box 348, Folder 4033)
    - Hong Kong - Specs, Budgets, Schedules (Box 348, Folder 4034)
    - Mandala - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 4035)
    - Mandala - Correspondence JNN, 1995-1996 (Box 348, Folder 4036)
    - Mandala - Design, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 4037)
    - Mandala - Exhibit, 1996-1997 (Box 348, Folder 4038)
    - Mandala - Public Relations, Press, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 4039)
    - Mandala - Product for Bookstore, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 4040)
    - Mandala - Exhibit Bills, 1997 (Box 348, Folder 4041)
    - Mandala - Returns, 1997-1998 (Box 348, Folder 4042)
    - Mandala - Invite (Box 348, Folder 4043)
    - Mandala - Bills Paid (Box 348, Folder 4044)
    - Mandala - Contents (Box 348, Folder 4045)
    - Mandala - Manuscript (Box 348, Folder 4046)
    - Mandala - Backmatter (Box 348, Folder 4047)
    - Mandala - Drafts (Box 349, Folder 4048-4049)
    - Mandala - Permissions, 1997 (Box 349, Folder 4050)
    - Mandala - Contracts (Box 349, Folder 4051)
    - Mandala - Co-Publishers (Box 349, Folder 4052)
    - Mandala - Specs, Budgets, Schedules (Box 350, Folder 4053)
    - Mandala - Invoices, Expenses (Box 350, Folder 4054)
    - Romance of the Taj Mahal (TAJ) - Labels (Box 350, Folder 4055)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Insurance (Box 350, Folder 4056)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Loan Agreements (Box 350, Folder 4057)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Loan Agreements (Box 350, Folder 4058)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Financing, Budget (Box 351, Folder 4059)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Publicity (Box 351, Folder 4060)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Art Programs (Box 351, Folder 4061)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Fact Sheet, 1984-1985 (Box 351, Folder 4062)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Correspondence with Lenders (Box 351, Folder 4063)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Correspondence with Lenders (Box 351, Folder 4064)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Requests for Support (Box 352, Folder 4065)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Related Activity (Box 352, Folder 4066)
    - Japanese Calligraphy - Humor In Japanese Art (Box 352, Folder 4067)
    - Permissions, 1992-1996 (Box 352, Folder 4068)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Catalogue Shipping, 1993 (Box 352, Folder 4069)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Catalogue Bills Paid (Box 352, Folder 4070)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Catalogue Photos (Box 352, Folder 4071)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Video (Box 352, Folder 4072)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Exhibition Bills Paid (Box 352, Folder 4073)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Exhibition, 1992-1993 (Box 352, Folder 4074)
    - Gods, Guardians and Lovers Exhibit - Visitor Survey (Box 352, Folder 4075)
    - Traditions-Tensions - McEvilley Essay (Box 352, Folder 4076)
    - Traditions-Tensions - Artist Biographies (Box 353, Folder 4077)
    - Traditions-Tensions - Front Matter (Box 353, Folder 4078)
    - Traditions-Tensions - Apinan Overview Essay (Box 353, Folder 4079)
    - Traditions-Tensions - Supangkat, Indones Essay (Box 353, Folder 4080)